1. The change I made to make the game work with Python 3:
	a. In 'adventure.py', line 37, I changed ' raw_input ' to ' input ' which make it can work in Python 3.
	b. In 'play.py' line 3, I changed input argument from 'data' to 'gameData' and in line 9, I changed 'data to 'gameData'. This change doesn't affect if the program can run. It just for making the argument name clearer. 
	c. I delete the # from 'text_walks.py' line 9. Then in 'walkthrough1.txt' line 863, I changed the 'adventure.resume(save file)' to 'play.resume(save file)'.
	d. I delete the # from 'text_walks.py' line 10. Then in walkthrough2.txt' line 1172, I changed the 'adventure._game.clock1' to 'play._game.clock1'.

2. The author used class, modules and comments.
	Class and modules are used to separate concerns and make the program more readable and easier understand by other authors.
	Comments are used to clarify specific meaning.

3. The author uses many meaningful names, such as 'adventure.py', 'game.py' and 'model.py'
	'Adventure.py' is the main program of the game. 
	'game.py' saves the design of the game itself.
	'model.py' has two classes, 'Move' and 'Room'. 'Move' is actions from one place to another, and 'Room' shows the location when we play the game. 
    	
	Some unclear names like 'loop()' in 'adventure.py' line 19 are very common used in any structure     of loops, which is confusing.

4. Function that only do one thing.
	accumulate_message(dictionary, n, line) in 'data.py' line 54. It only add new message to the dictionary. 
    Function that do more than one thing.
	resume(savefile, quiet=False) in 'play.py' line 29. It do three things in a function, resuming the game, installing words and checking if it is quiet.

5. Function 'section1(data, n, *etc) has side effects since it does't return the result after changing.

6. The "play" function in 'play.py' line 11 and the "resume" function in 'play.py' line 29 are very similar. The major difference of them is that "play" starts a new game and 'resume' resumes a saved game.  Many of the lines in these functions are repeated. Maybe we can use a different function to start the game and another function to save a present game, which can eliminate repetition of the program.

7. The program uses exception handling in 'adventure.py' in line 42-47. Player can use Control + C to terminate the game mandatory.

8. Class 'Object' has more functionality. It contains many orders that player can use to control the game, like carry, drop, hide and destroy.

9. Class 'Dwarf' in 'model.py' line 165 is an example that is not so cohesive. It keeps information of dwarves and pirates, and pirates are subclass of dwarves, which is counter-intuitive. This design make 'Dwarf' responsible for keeping track of both dwarves and privates, while making the 'Pirate' class useless.

10. 'game.py' line 278,286. It seems that the author believe everyone is familiar with Fortran, and the author use a lot of Fortran code reference.
	In 'game.py' line21, the author say 'how many times to "sorry", but i am not allowed...'. it can be a confusing and long comment.
	In general, the author makes comments very clear, like in 'game.py' line 39-51. These comment clearly demonstrate what this part for.

11. In 'game.py' function describe_location(), the author separated many different cases by a blank line, which make it clear.

12. The unit tests provided with the program runs fine, but there were two issues with the walkthroughs. I have made the following change to make the walkthroughs work:
 +a. Uncommented line 9 and 10 in 'test_walks.py' to run a unit test on the two walkthroughs.
 +b.  In 'walkthrough1.txt' line 863, I changed the 'adventure.resume(save file)' to 'play.resume(save file)'.
 +c. In walkthrough2.txt' line 1172, I changed the 'adventure._game.clock1' to 'play._game.clock1'. +d. There is some mistake in README.txt. When player want to save the game, they only need to input 'save advent' instead of 'save advent.save'. This problem can be solved by changing the word in README.txt.

	
