1.   In adventure.py, at line 37 change raw_input() to input() in order to follow Python 3 syntax 
     In test_walks.py, uncomment the last two tests.addTests() to make sure we are also taking test on the walkthrough1.txt and walkthrough2.txt
     In walkthrough1.txt and walkthrough2.txt, import adventure at the beginning
     In walkthrough1.txt[149], change >>>adventure.resume(savefile) to >>>play.resume(savefile)
     In walkthrough2.txt[242], change >>>adventure._game.clock1 to >>> play._game.clock1


2.   Author used different modules, classes and functions to efficiently structure the program for making it easy to read, maintain and test. Here are some examples, play.py import module game. game.py has a class Game under it, data.py has the class Data. And almost every module in the program has their own functions, which are small, and each function only does one thing. 



3.   Yes, author used meaningful names. For instance, in game.py:
is_dead(line34): describe is the play dead or not
max_deaths(line36): tell us how many times one player can die maximally in the game
the method inventory() (line88):tell us what the player is holding in the game
     In data.py, section1/section2/section3…section12 are NOT meaningful names.



4.   Yes, there are lots of examples, and most of the functions in the program only do one thing at a time. Like in play.py, method resume() restored the game from the last one.And in game.py, is_dark() method only tells whether it’s dark or not. 
     Instead, method section3() in data.py does a lot of things within a single function. section3() does lots of conditional statement for m and n, also also make a new move object and modifies its attributes. Those are too much thing in one function, and could be separated into several functions. 



5.   In game.py, function move_to(self, newloc=None)clearly has side effects,as it’s changing the value of a variable; after we call move_to(), the variable new_loc will be changed.



6.   In play.py, line20~21 and line 32~33：
		from game import Game
    		from prompt import install_words
we import the same thing twice in different functions, which can be merged into one. As the convention for program, we should import all needed modules at the beginning.



7.   Yes, in adventure.py line41-46:
if __name__ == "__main__":
    try:
        loop()
    except EOFError:
        pass
when I type python -m adventure mygame, program runs my previously stored game. But if I mistakenly type the wrong name, like: python -m adventure myga, then it will cause the program to terminate abnormally



8.   In the model.py, the class Object serves over more than one piece of functionality. It represents an object in the game, but also has the functionality of carry, drop, hide and destroy. 



9.   In game.py, the class Game holds lots of instance variables, but each method only manipulate a few of them, so it’s not that cohesive. It’s likely to break class into several sub classes.



10.  Generally, the comments are using pretty clear and straightforward, make the code easier to read and maintain. Each module will be given a comment at the beginning which tells us what this module is used for. However, there are bad comments existing, for example in game.py, line21-37, all the attributes under class Game following with the explanation comments, but the name of variable is already clear and straightforward, makes the comments redundant.



11.  In model.py, line165-185,class Dwarf and class Pirate are related, so the class Pirate is coded right after Dwarf, which is keep related thing together. Also there is a blank line between them, which is a visual clue the identity a separate concept.
     In data.py, line74-95, variable m&n are defined at the beginning, following by a blank line, then set the condition for m. After a blank line, set the condition for n.



12.   The unittest passed successfully after I uncomment last two test in test_walks.py and In walkthrough1.txt[149], change adventure.resume(savefile) to play.resume(savefile) In walkthrough2.txt[242], change adventure._game.clock1 to play._game.clock1. The F.T.R.S.T. criteria is fast, independent, repeatable, self-validating and timely, and in our case, the test is：
      (1).Independent to each other since if we change the order of tests or comment out any one of the test, the tests are still working good.
      (2).Repeatable in any environment and the outcome is still good.
      (3).Self-validating since each test is either pass or fail.
      (4).Timely which can be told in the README.txt file that the tests were written during development.
      (5).Fast but not fast enough, since I ran 16 tests in 13.269s.
                 